Curriculum Vitae Jackson Kent

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: Jackson Kent

Date of Birth: 26 November 1993

Address: 100 Byangum Road, Murwillumbah NSW

Email: jacksonkent70@gmail.com

Mobile: 0416252611

BIO

I am a highly motivated, well organised individual with over ten years experience in the hospitality industry. Having worked in managerial and wholesale roles in the specialty coffee world for seven years, I moved into a technician/support role at Brewtech. Brewtech is an industry leading coffee machine and grinder servicing company based in Melbourne. I was the first team member in Sydney, a team which has now grown to six people, in quick succession.

Music is another great passion of mine. The completion of my Bachelor Degree in Creative Technology at JMC Academy two years ago led to my involvement in an internship at Parliament Studios, Leichhardt. Subsequently I am currently working as a freelance audio engineer and producer. I am also a professional musician, playing both sessions and performing in bands that have toured Australia, Canada and the United States.

I am currently completing the Coding Bootcamp at the University of Sydney in conjunction with Edx. I am in the final stages of the course and have covered a multitude of in demand concepts: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js, Express.js and React. Moving into the software engineering and development space feels like a natural progression of my skills, one which I'm extremely excited about.

EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS

- Coding Bootcamp USYD Statement of Completion (2023)
- Bachelor of Creative Technology (2016) JMC Academy
- Diploma of Creative Technology (2015) JMC Academy
- HSC (2011) Cronulla High School

EMPLOYMENT

<u>Brewtech</u> - September 2020 - Present Technician/Sales/Support

<u>Coffee Supreme Sydney</u> - November 2018 - September 2020 Technician/Deliveries/Sales/Support

<u>West End Espresso Jannali</u> - September 2016 - November 2018 Head Barista

<u>Pilgrims Cafe Cronulla</u> - January 2016 - June 2016 Barista/Waiter/Kitchen Hand

<u>Bianchinis Cafe Cronulla/Gymea</u> - January 2015 - December 2015 Head Barista

More details and referees available upon request.